These days the heat has crossed all limits. If you go out, you
die. It feels as if the
sun is sipping at us through a straw.
That's why one has to
think ten times before going from office to home or from home to office or anywhere else.
But what if you have to buy something? Groceries,
food, clothes, everything is available online,
but is health insurance available? Yes, hello,
namaste, and welcome to Policy One. Today, where was
I talking about insurance with Sonali?
Oh, yes, clothes, milk, eggs, vegetables,
everything is available online. And now with Policy One,
you can get health insurance from the comfort of your home.
But which one is the best in the market? You will have to
study a lot to find out.
No, because Policy One has made it easier for you. We have but
you. Top
five health insurance for
2024. We will tell you only the best health insurance
available in the market. Now, you
know that treatment costs in hospitals have
increased a lot, that is why a
health insurance
policy has become necessary to cover emergency expenses. That is why we have brought the
best and top health insurance for
you. First Aditya Billa Active Health
Platinum  Policy: This insurance policy covers
medical expenses ranging from ₹2 lakh to ₹1 crore. The
policy's network hospital
list includes over 10,000 hospitals.
For anyone looking for a comprehensive health insurance plan, the
Aditya Birla Active Health Plan would be a good fit.
It is a plan that covers diseases like
diabetes, asthma, and high blood pressure from the day of policy purchase.
Second Star Health Senior Citizen Red
Carpet Health Policy: This policy ranges from ₹1 lakh to
₹1 lakh. This plan covers over 12,000
hospitals. This policy is
specifically designed for people aged 60 years and above.
This policy is available for one, two, and three-
year durations.
Furthermore, this policy also offers lifelong renewal.
Thirdly, a company whose name itself is enough is
also
on the list of top health insurance policies. Guess which
popular brand we are talking about?
Let's simplify things a bit. Listen to this music.
Yes, it's ICICI Arogya Sanjivani
Policy. In this, you will get insurance coverage for diseases
like Covid, Cataract, Family Health, Diabetes ...  This plan offers coverage
ranging from ₹1 lakh to ₹5 lakh.
This policy has
over 7,500 network hospitals. The
fourth plan, which
I've previously detailed, is the
Star Family Health Optima Plan.
This health insurance policy provides
health insurance coverage for your entire family on a family floater basis. Its
special feature is
that this plan requires a lower premium.
If the policyholder is involved in
an accident, the
sum insured automatically
increases to approximately ₹5 lakh. This policy
also covers hospital expenses, room rent, and medicine.
Fifth is ADFC Ergo Health
Suraksha. Last but not least, this
policy covers health insurance from ₹1 lakh to ₹10 lakh.
This plan has over 13,000 hospitals in the country
under its network. This plan offers optimized coverage with no
age limit. The policy also covers day
care, AYUSH treatment, and organ donation expenses. It
also offers maternity
benefits.  It also pays for mental health and ambulance
expenses. Now you have to choose
one of these
plans as per your requirements. As they say, we are one
decision away from a totally different life.
So this is your chance to make a change in your
life. Buy good health insurance
and protect yourself and your loved ones till then.
Bye bye, take care and be happy.
[Music]
Insure B